Welcome, welcome
To the circus that escaped the silo
Where tarot cards fly and trolls get tried
You in the pan of verse, baby
I'm Father Scythe, the cat daddy
Scythe in the building, cards on debt
Tarot spread wide like a hackle on the net
Got linoa in the corner, claws out for lies
Tricks, plot and chaos with those cosmic eyes
Lola screening on the chest, Rudy got flared
Mumbles in the mix, we don't play fair
Chat blowing up like divine confessions
True bombs drop, no time for confessions
You on logic, we bend it, drama, we mend it
Panel full of chaos, but the vibes transcending
If a troll wanna bark, we clap back politely
With Andromelius, watchin' nightly
Welcome to Psych Awakens TV
It's crazy, it's loud, it's bizarre
Believe me, we laugh, we scream
We read the unseen
By the psychic hat daddy king of the stream
Welcome to Psych Awakens TV
We're truth and madness
If the same T, it's a family affair
It's dysfunction supreme
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Pan-averse world call
Bring your weirdest takes
Listen to chat, she a mystery queen DJ Electric got the beat so clean
Beat her with the panther, strength divine She teams chaos with the stare and the line
We don't do fake, this tribe's too real We roast you kindly, but the love's a deal
Got minds with swords, keeping gates tight They swing truth like justice in the moon like
Gifted subs, yeah the cold keeps growing Community wild, but the energy's flowing
It's crazy, it's loud, it's bizarre, believe me
We laugh, we scream, we read the unseen
Father, psych, the cat, daddy, king of the stream
Welcome to Psych Awaken's TV
With truth, the madness, if the same tea
It's a family affair, it's dysfunction
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Cards flip, candles drip, shadows in the mist
Trolls talk slick, but they cease to exist
We're half chaos, half or a cool flame
And every night's a ritual in Psyche's name
No scripts, no filters, no chill in Psyche
We stream raw truth till the morning light
So grab your tea, grab your mic and vibe
We the strangest fam that I've ever seen
This ain't YouTube, this is an underworlds talk show, you are now initiated.
Oh my god, brother guy.
Hey Lula, no don't use that.
It's all you got up there for a second
Then
Cut I'm sorry. I'm sorry, bro
Oh, oh, you like it. I'm another good one. Here's the new song
I'll preempt I'll preempt that yeah, there's a special ghosty here
Cook that shit down. Why is it so far up?
Oh, let's go!
Thank you, Sonic. Looks beautiful.
In some way ghost about to die
Heroes allowed like thunder on caffeine drop the stacks crack and jokes keep in the scene clean
The crowd starts howling the trolls start crying ghost just grins
Let's fucking go and now we're flying
He's chaos
What the hell are we talking about?
He held me down when the sky lost it's you
They can't see the light he threw in my storm
You do have a mission to crash out?
Yeah!
Go stone ready did it took the whole crowd
Heart of gold boys of fire
When gold shows up the stakes get higher
Dumb dumb that's his war cry sound
Every day he gets spun right round round
When the chat goes cold he brings it loud
They talk slick why is he still around
Why did it make the images or no Indian Indian Indian? No, no
Yeah, well, I like India
Is that like Indian music and I think it's catchy it's like ball kind of Bollywood like
Catchy and I like it. Well, if you like it. All right, I'll give you the pass it, but I don't appreciate it man
It's not just Indian. I fused it with like I use like three styles usually I fuse like three styles together
You know what sir? I can see you know what sir you are the mess reader you win this one. I concede you win
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Oh
Yeah, I mean, so I'm gonna start with Leo scenario Leo and by the way, you know, we're not gonna do tonight
Well, I'm gonna let saying that is up here. Oh, you are or J1. No, no, no, we're not or J1
Because saying that is he was it was he did you see he just show
Did I see what?
Be this chat. Oh be this chat what he was in there saying things about me well saying that was right up in that mother fucker and then
Jay running fucking join
Even though we all couldn't say a fucking word
Yeah, I'll retarded. Let me ask you a quote. Are you do you want to put this on or can I ask you a question?
All right, as you say it's an open panel. I mean I was you're not gonna let everybody join but it's just open
panel everyone's talking shit about that and like
Like it's not that open isn't like
Like and but here's the thing though
You're not letting people join how is that open you said open you know I'm saying everyone joining except for KZ
Because he owes porn bombers. There's always exceptions to the rules her
If you say there's an open panel, you better be able to join unless you're a you know a degenerate. I'm saying yeah
Yeah discuss you
I want to not let you join because I want to talk to her.
All she did was run and fuck.
I, now I'm getting on your shit.
Be calm, Brennan, I'm not gonna beat up you.
She's all fucking dumb fuck.
Oh, well.
You shouldn't there.
You shouldn't even think about that.
You should do better for yourself, sir.
No, well, I mean, I'm not even worried about anybody else.
I'm just concerned about that.
All right, let's have a good time.
Yeah, we're having a good time.
Let's have a good time.
Yeah
Well, would you like me to call you beautiful the gray hairs we're getting older brother. We're getting old
Well, you're like 12 years younger than me. So
Well, we're getting old but like listen, would you agree with me stress has a lot to do with that, too?
Well, yeah, but I think they're pretty good. I'm like my hair
Technically you can be a 20-year-old if you have a lot of stress, but tech my ex-girlfriend's dad
He went great 18 years old believe it or not
Before that, but yeah, he was completely great
My brother's I don't think my brother's I think my brother's almost 40
I think he's like 30 that's your brother days for a living if I can ask if you
He worked as like a you know doing
These sets for like Netflix projects order brother
He's a younger brother
Guess what my older brothers see a celebrity. No, he's a cop
He's going into FBI
Even a copper like that's like what like eight fucking years, I think
My uncle was the sergeant of the part department here, so
We use we spend your looks on here
Yeah, what do you think about this guy right here?
Your face is blurred by the way, I don't know if you care about your face support
What do you wind up to stop the gay shit here?
Let me say there's a guy I know and you like women and don't actually look fucking but then like you don't like women
I know you like women
I do like them. I like them a lot. You love them. You love them. You want to be with them?
Are you trying to hypnotize me? Don't lie. Don't lie to me.
Oh, you just love them like all you start to hang up. I love them like sisters.
I don't think we can be friends anymore, brother. I think this is the end of our friendship.
I love you like a
I love you like a you should have said brother
Don't say God in here dude. Don't say God
We can love each other like a brother, I mean we've known each other for how long now, it's at least been like what two years one year
Probably about a little over a year
Yeah, a little over a year brother. We don't get along
We don't get along. We actually don't have to sing but
I would like to see that we're friends maybe we're not friends
We fight but the makeup sex is incredible
Dude see this is why I don't fuck it. This is why I don't fucking you say some gay ass shit, bro. Stop doing that
You know, you know, I feel uncomfortable with this top scene
I just ate this only flurry. I'm sorry, I'm eating like hot, I'm eating high on this.
Yeah, you would eat this dick, yeah?
Now stop saying gay shit!
Here.
Can't you just be my friend? Do you know what friends are?
Yeah, I'm not flurry, I'm gonna pick some.
Maybe friends. Come on, friends.
Oh, I'm finna crush now.
You're finna crush.
It's flurry and it's crooked.
I'm finna crush.
Peace, though.
Actually, you know what for your chat. Can we say you love ghosts real quick? I
love ghosts
That was weird I don't know why I asked you that I that was so I love putting ghosts in my mouth
Then dude, dude, I literally just asked you to stop it. It's like an ecto. Stop the gay shit
Ecto cooler. He's like slammer
Love it. Would you like to put my fish in your mouth? Yes, please
Would you like to be punching the fucking face? Oh
Hey, hey Mason get up here it protect me from this
No, no, no Mason. What do you mean? Let me my main name of this. That's my name
No, no, no, no, are you wearing a star?
Help me Mason help me
Okay, I fix it now. You remember all those long nights. We're alone. You called me you said baby. I'm gonna lay with you
Yeah, I said you're gonna be the you're gonna be the a little
Yeah, I was gonna be the spoon I was gonna eat you. I'm the big spoon. Yeah
We could have a spoon fight
And put our spoons together. Well, you never bring a fucking fork to a spoon fight
All I do is bring my big mouth
How big is it?
Right now
It's okay to be gay and stop the gay shit. Okay
There's one time a handsome you love a handsome little devil. Thank you
You kind of look like you can only gay jacked up John Wick
John Wick a little bit. Oh
Yeah, I don't look at now nah
I didn't you ought to give you the matrix already gave you the matrix
Do you know you would have now John wait though you nobody can be on this level. I might use that I
Would have distracted you like to lead you with the red dress, right?
Okay, do you have red I'm not wearing underwear am I I'm wearing
Dude, I that's like to by the way, that's strike two do it a third time. I'm leaving. Okay. It's okay. I'm sorry. What are you wearing underwear?
Yeah, I'm dead. Is that like three? I think that's like three, not last three.
I think it's three, man. I think you're talking last question.
If it's going to count as three, you have to tell me, like, is it boxers or briefs?
Don't ask me no dumbass questions, bro.
Are you wearing boxers or briefs?
None of your fucking business, here.
Can you send me them in the mail?
Yeah, I'll send you here right now. Stop asking me the ASQS complicated.
Okay.
I don't wash make sure you I don't wash you just keep fresh off. I'm not gonna wash now. I'm not gonna wash now. I'm not gonna wash now. I'm not gonna wash now. I'm not gonna wash now. I'm not gonna wash now. I'm not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna wash now. Not gonna
No, no, no, no, he's gonna perform on us again. He never performed on me
If he promised not to perform on us, will it? Yeah, don't fucking dumbass
I'm gonna marry a dumb dumb. Oh my gosh. You should marry them
I'm gonna have many years
Go look at psyche cigar and dumb dumb
Calling me a seagull. Hey, I'm gonna. By the way Tony. My, my, my, you have to fix your avatar
You're gonna fix your avatar. It's not showing at the nipple. It's just a white circle. I
Don't see a nipple or a white circle. I see it. I see it. Yeah, nobody better to come up. Yeah, I see how I see
I see the tip of Alexander's cock in the photo. Oh
Yum yum yum yum yum. I want to eat that
What are you? What are you doing?
I didn't tell you to porn mom anybody. Oh, oh, oh, yeah, I want you to defend me. I didn't want you to
porn mom. Mason, Mason was like, you want me to defend you psyche?
One shirt, Mason? The guy with one shirt? Mason?
With the blue dumb shirt that he never changes that guy. Get up here. Get up here fight with Alexander
I think what a freak. Well, he doesn't change his shirt. I don't know
I think he's smart enough. I mean if he's a drummer you have to have some kind of noodles up there
You know, you know how to drum
Sure, they're all dedicated to drumming and not to you know to fast to fashion, but I think that's fine
Ghost came back look at him
Where's fucker Roni?
Sorry, she's funky, man. I mean
He's so funny. Hey tea doesn't want to move in
Call leader so when you change the name or a channel to call
Remember and that means we have to you know
You'd have sex at least one time. You said to look go lay down in the bed and close your eyes
But on a blindfold I come in handcuffed you and sector dick and then that's it
But but it could be anybody stuck in my dick, right? It could be
No, that's the test we need a bigger wig, but I guess you'll know if there's a list of 20 people and 10 or guys 10 of girls and you say the
Initiation is you gotta close your eyes. I'm gonna suck it big
It could be Vita it could be Vita suck my dick. It could be Stikey. It could be ghost. It could be paced
insane
Yeah, it could be anybody it could be anybody everybody's talking the car and that's the initiation you have to just take it
And whoever's lived and it's you'll never know you'll never know who's up you talk that
Maybe it was everybody that's freaky. Am I crazy bro? That's a little crazy, right? That's gay. Is that gay?
Well, what if someone like licks your butt?
I don't think the LES or someone that's like super homophobic will do that because they'll be like no one's talking my dick
But I don't know it's not a girl like right like that's gay. You're like half gay
But don't you just judge by the quality of blowjob and so what if it's like like you're here
But it could be a guy and it could be the best blowjob you ever had and you don't know what it is
could be could have a cock you know you never know it's like you know it's like I'll just
blow you in the bar bathroom I mean you I've had bad blowjobs man and I've had amazing
I know probably about women women are women are not very good they're old girls
you know what the best blowjob is you ever had a blowjob when they twirl their tongue
so they have your dick in their mouth and then they're twirling their tongue on the tip of your
cock yeah and it's like you ever do you ever like like this
Like pull out the guy. Oh, yeah, the gagging. I don't like that a girl. I choke him to death with the cock
I'm not a fan of that. I don't know
Don't buy that
We're stuck into like you tell me that they die. I don't like that
Okay, I didn't mean that I've been pulling like your pubic your pubi hair from the back of my throat because
It's scratchy
Pubi pubi hair. Yes
Do you have like, uh, I like central blow jobs just you know lake lake the shaft up and down
No team
There's an older man with like white hair like I didn't expect you to be so
Yeah, I heard I'm back my bad. I had a sneeze dude
My bad. Yeah, you're what Steve? I
Had a sneeze like five times. Oh, okay
Well, I
Like I think my problem is I'm a buddy Jake. You know how that would be, you know
Well, it's like yeah, I would use the dump-downs now she's done them
No, you sniffing a whack cocaine. You have to call me for the good stuff
Making your sneeze, okay
Don't don't act stupid, bro. I know exactly why you're squeezing shit, Ed
Because you bought some wack shit
How'd you what you you do online?
Why did you say you didn't let me back up here?
Why
That's a question for the ages. We're all pondering that at the moment. You, me, and Psycho, right?
No, would you like to?
We can all agree on that. Why did Psycho let me up? I think we can all align.
Yeah, say what? Would you like to leave? Much more often right now. Would you like to leave?
Whatever.
What are you going to do? Respectful, you.
Respectful?
You're dumb dumb ass.
Call me. Call big ghost dad. Go ahead.
Call me daddy. Never. I'd rather at least die. You're not gonna kick this. Jump over the bridge.
If he's going to become a daddy, call me daddy. Call me daddy.
Call me daddy. Call me daddy. Call me daddy.
Call me a good boy. Call me daddy, here.
How'd your daddy get sick? Thank you. Get a little back on your mind.
Uh-oh. I didn't actually mean that. I was actually just talking.
No, right out. You can... Well, dude, why are you here to spend thousands of feet of shit?
He's probably gonna point it on me as well.
Yeah, I am probably actually so listen
I'm looking through my room with X of cocks
My god
You guys are so funny
Crucible
No, I'm done
No, I don't want to run it. No. No, I don't
You don't want you don't want to run. I want you to leave I get plenty of enough money for you to be off of here
I don't want to talk right now. They even give you in sake of running your space. Is that what it is?
I'm intruding on your time. Can you get down there quick? Can I come back a little later ghost?
Well, listen kick him real quick and that's fine
Uh, well, I don't even trust him most of them if you give me your word
He gave me his word. I wouldn't trust him. I don't trust him. It's like you shouldn't
You'll call your daddy, but he won't
He left backstage. Well, that was weird to me
I should but no, he's gonna but it's your pain or why you want somebody
I'll be listening to poor Bobby dumb dumb. He's not gonna poor mommy, but he might call you daddy. Oh, he's never done
Let me ask you a question. He's never done it before
Okay, let me ask you a question now. We're getting the fucking algorithm against my brother. Let's do it
Has he ever poured on me before?
No
Alice has never poured on me. I can bring up by the way he did and I couldn't bring up evidence. Would you like me to show it?
Well, not if it's a cute picture of his cock and let's see good. Okay. If I I have to take time
I can like burn out, but he did
He it was as an accident and he paid me he paid a fine
It's not an accident. Well paid you how much how much money you paid me $30 because he porn bombed and then he um
Docs easy
He almost fucking took your channel all the way down
Well, you know, it's your channel worth $30 or you
Control for it. I was able to listen. I don't appreciate that. Well, listen, here's my point
I knew what the fuck I was talking about. That's why I asked you that question. I knew for a fact he formed on you
That's why I say I I tend to like know things before I ask it
But is that dude not fucking a darty he's not gonna like fucking take your channel about channel down the first chance he gets
Well, I mean, I have to just watch it
It's like it's like having a pit bull
Why are you running not me? But why are you running? I'd be doing a tunnel
Alice is here and then
He's a fucking nobody he likes the porn bomb. He's a piece of shit. He's a retard it
I mean, I'm not even like you shouldn't even let him over here to defend himself at this point like I
Don't talk now so I can pass like year year now like fuck him
This stuff's you know corn bomb
But you seem to all 30 bucks you get 30 bucks one time. Okay. I mean, I guess that's good
He's still a piece of shit when bomber he did show a pic on screen
Well, what did he not do that?
Yeah, it's not like I'm beat it with 157 people in her chat. I'm sitting here with like, you know
Nobody nobody coming up everyone chose her side over me, but it's okay
Well, they want a man in this world that like this said that's the only reason why yeah, I
Can't remember again. Hey Mason. Hey Mason. Do you want to see look at this even pussy Mason?
That's a nice pussy sir
It's Lola. Hi. That's a big pussy, sir
Lola, you're she's mom. Okay. It's Lola. Is there a rat over there?
You brought a rat in and it's not even inside or what you eat the thing you eat that rat
What did you do? You know what the crazy things like is and I think Mason probably like to talk about this
I don't know if he's trying to join but
Dolls came from whilst we all know that but you know cats came from like bigger cats and like tigers and shit. Yeah
Well, they gave them these things are killing animals. Do you look like a tiger or like a fucking lion? That's what they came from
Right. Well, this is it. Yeah, but yeah
So so the house cat the domestic house cat came from the African wild cat
And you know what where dogs came from they all came from a common ancestor, you know what the common ancestor of every dog is
Of the welfare of the people of the dog
Um
No good the great wolf the great wolf is the is the ancestor every time I was correct
Maybe I've been and the cats are from an African wild cat. Yeah, Mason's Mason. I didn't say I see my cat
I said to my pussy good to say put Mason what you like to join sir, Mason come up here. It goes once to talk
He's a he's friendly. He's not gonna mention you guys don't mention his shirt, okay?
I'm not gonna mention your shirt or your autism or your retardedness or how you're so fucking sleepy
Listen you can't hold that cat up in the respect where they came from
Well, that's sure you can hold a tiger up like that, but what would you like a saber to tiger up like that?
Oh, yeah, you wouldn't fucking yeah, no they're extinct, but what if it was a thunder cat?
Sabotage is extinct. Diarrhox are extinct, but they it's many many a thought of hundreds of years, bro
Your ghost ghost your avatars not showing on my TV on my phone. I see the TV. I don't know my TV
It's just a white circle
Victoria Gotti and it's a Victoria Gotti. That's actually the real Alex whatever your worst nightmare is put it in that picture
Cuz that's what I envy
Yeah, I'm just saying
Hold on why do you eat cheeseburgers constantly? How did you get so fat and when you hit like
You sound heavy sir first of all, why do you have with a fake top? Why are you such a mess? Why do I spring you up?
Why are you so retarded? Why are you so dumb?
Why are you still talking when i'm talking? Why do you feel like
Is like a power trip you don't have power like you want to run one. It's not burning up again. Go ahead
Let's run it. Let's run it dog. Let's run one. I've got the wrong one. No, I'm sure cycle. Let me run it
I'm running like you run. I run psyche psyche. It'll be collateral damage. Thank you
Thank you an accident broke as I'm running
Did you like the world one would you like to sit there and shut the fuck up?
Exactly
Why is he even back here? Why do you want me back to the drummer?
Hasn't changed his shirt since you joined me so the drummer can join not you Alex you dumb fuck
But Mason hasn't changed his shirt, bro. You want to sit up? He will smell it
Boy
You're probably smells like shit, right you're diapers
Why
Are you
I got
We don't
How funny you those you're gonna get kicked bro, we don't
Who's we you like there's no one up here? Oh, that's what a dickhead
Like you're not a panel full of people
People up here like we don't care Alex. You're talking to yourself. You fat fuck
I know you're talking about it. I did call you. Why don't you give us $2,000? So everyone can just die right now
Okay
And they
Yeah, bro, you know, that's my favorite
Arbiter
Drop another bomb on their head
Right now I will match you. I will match your super chat. Oh, you're in a mess. All right, let's not match
50 we do 25 I'm not rich like you go store. Okay. What do you 25 get 25 no matter? Yeah
Yeah, I'm gonna sell site 25 and you'll match it
as a super chat on the screen either you're gonna get you just open up your mouth even give 25 or must have my fingers
You're gonna be gone. I'll match you though
All right, so I got a cell psychone's
Okay, thank you
Please
So I got a job
So
I'll bet your 20 if you give it we'll let you back up sucky drop me
Okay, yeah, if you get $20, we'll let you back up them fuck and I
Matter of fact, I'm ready to double it
Is that fair I think that's
That's very fucking retard dumbass motherfucker. Do you know what the fuck he's talking about?
By the way, where the fuck his thing is he's fucking shit and beat us being a by the way
There's another guy that's fucking a lot of shit
What did he say?
Just over there like I agree with them and shit. You didn't really talk shit, but you agree
Yeah, I know he's like, oh, thank you's crazy
Yeah, keep saying like I need to go to like I'm the type of motherfucker that I'm joined like how is he crazy?
That's room one, but ever since I've been saying that's been with a year now like all your psyche boy
Well fucking you know debate me. I guarantee the no
By the way, I got your boy, uh, the world's name happens remember the dude that works in debate school
Yes
Yeah
Let's do it come on up thing
Well, I don't know if he's banned, but he's not bad for my my
You don't think I mean probably good idea. Why'd you bet? Well, actually I take that back. Why'd you say anything?
I mean the thing that is our fighting. Oh, yeah, that's him. Yeah, but saying I mean he's
He's a dumb ass. He just post about like sure to you
Right, I mean he was like he kept like putting kind of like it's like just like talking about stuff
I was like trying to
Yeah, it was a little bit about you and stuff, but before he was like
Yeah
What that man saying join
Yeah, I'm a school of Athens and not here right now. I don't know. I don't think it was
Thing that is I don't know. I think he's in beat us chat right now. Yeah, I know he is
Can I oh, I can't hear that word. Sorry. I almost said it. Sorry
Hmm. It's okay. I like it. I like it when you call me them private
Yeah
You're gonna go
I
Can you I'm gonna call you sugar. I love it here. I'm gonna finish the go song or no
I already put it down. Okay. Let me call you. Let me call you baby
Yeah
application
Yeah, you started it
Well, no, brother. Fuck you started you started. I'm gonna finish it
You started it, baby
Okay handsome good looking
Click like you look like a little grease here now like it
Yeah, I'm like Fonzie. I'm like I'm like a
You're like the retirement version of
My precious
That was fucking rude night. That was fucked up. And I shouldn't have said it. That was
That was fucked up. It's like them. That's like the scariest worst character in the world. What is this one's jerking off backstage?
Someone's jerking off from me. I see us. Who is that? Let me see. Let me see. Who is that? It was Nick
Rejurking off just now backstage dick
No, oh this is this I can ask this guy a question was this name were you on the left? Were you on?
Was the TPP?
Hey, look at this. He's turning around. We have a fit check. Hey, hey, yeah, no, his name
I know this guy Alex gets back on by the way, does he pay?
Well, how much he paid I'll pay how much he paid just let me 20 bucks. I'll send you 40
Well, he's not even up yet
You want to go dance or damn?
Wait till he gets up. Wait till he gets up and finishes him.
Okay, that's fine.
Uh, Bernie Joy, was your name not Brett?
Like on the, you were on TPP, correct?
It was a guy named mcdonalds and fries number two, okay, and then that
Answer a fucking question. I thought it was nick johnson because he came up at the same time. It's always a suspicious
No, I saw Nick's butt once though. I heard the nick johnson song goes to like that song
Okay, we play it one time no fuck that I'm playing go song this panel year I played Nick Johnson song one time
Okay, here's one time
You don't like it
That's me.
Sorry for the wrong shit.
SuperMod of the PsyCyber
Body of the PsyCyber
Wild and free keeper of the live stream sanity if madness is art, then he's the verse
So good
Thank you for inspiring
Supermod of the psyche
Superm Nick is supermod of the sack give her hey Nick. You're my pussy
See my pussy. Well happy to go. He just gave me two dollars a no party like a gaudy party
It's like a ditty party except
There's more wheelchairs and a ramp outside. I'm just kidding. No, that's not a really bad. Okay, because it was a super joke
I'm just kidding. I got he's got it's not wheelchair
the boys
pose as Scotland detective
oh
Sherlock Holmes which is like a blow job sir
hello
I think I lost Nick
uh oh
Oh, hold on. Oh, you were talking about something else. I'm sorry. I thought I thought we're doing role play
I thought you were short columns. I was an inspector
You
Hey, Nick, we're not watching the entire Warren Brothers catalog right now, what are you doing?
Backing first your eyes and pulling your pants.
You're not a gentleman.
It's like slapping each other.
Now, if you don't fight, explain.
Poise place.
Yeah, here it is.
Your fantasy just want to slap other guys?
No.
No rule.
it's an AI. It's an AI. It's an AI that I'm working on. Oh, what about how about you make
an AI that lets make you love? How about that one?
Oh, yeah, don't you want to come on computer?
My old computer
This is the best of the easiest to have that technology
Love gay phone on there
You know we do a good job. They might promote us to be detected.
They might not have that updated on there.
Yeah, that's why you do. Okay.
Well, it's okay.
It's gonna get the new model updated.
It's funny just to see Shil.
It's easy, son.
It's important to me. I kind of like what you like to see in the photo though.
I
You like when they like when there's like a woman with like five black guys
Or what this is loud shit? Oh, I'm sorry
Who me or the time on that? Oh, it's okay
This Larry he's gonna get pop
Can't pop oh it is
It is like like sexual get him get him out. He's gonna be at the anapanda party. Hold on a second
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Hold on. I don't I don't know
anything about it. I don't know
anything about it. Hold on. Like
Kyle Massey. Who? Uh that that
was a pretty nasty situation.
I'm having a McDonald's. Where's
Good old backpack orange
Nothing goes better. You bite in the dumpster
No, I
Just put it in my backpack from the house. Oh, we forgot it still in there
Didn't match it so I don't know if you could do math goes I did $20 you did for
That's not matching anything. You really want it. You want to go dollar? No, no, no
You said if I drop something you match it you like to do not
Because you know what? I'll make this thing right now. I'm not talking shit. I gave warm rain on you
But you didn't match it so you just like
You lie
Not matching 20 you're still missing
Come back in my eyes
I said I'll match it. I mean I know what I don't want to hear that
Alex so much. I'll even drop 40. I'll even do double
This guy did four hours for us. You got so much money. I gave that's like how much money I'll be
When dick, I don't give a fuck what you gave in the past we're talking about now and when I said I'm gonna drop 20 you match
You said yes, and you did
I gave way more
Would you like me to give her money I
Guess I guess like just I got you bang
No, I get it
Hold on you make $300 a week you give it to psych and it makes you look like
This guy doesn't have money
Give sick the psyche on the weekend and everyone thinks he's rich
It's giving psyche is $2 an hour wage paycheck
Holy shit Batman, okay, cool. I gave way
Not sat there and shut the fuck up. Do you know the fuck you're coming up dumb dumb
You didn't match it bro.
You didn't match it man.
You didn't match my 20.
I'll give way more than I...
Not tonight after you said you'll match it.
They got a kill with the game.
Oh god, you need to drop right now and
Ask me to apologize when I pump I'm just dumb ass or whatever the poachers you apologize to me for lying
How much you didn't keep your word. No, I chopped 20 you didn't match it
So you're a scumbag loser as of now as of this moment
You're a scumbag loser liar if you drop and sign psyche 20 and match my 20 then
You will redeem yourself
There you go fat boy go to fucking get the credit card out fat man
Look at johnson with his tits this guy needs a bra
He thinks he looks like you know, he thinks he walks out
He's still like, you know, how much body fat is on there? There's a lot of body fat. I can squeeze it on you. Yeah
Callista flock heart would be jealous
Okay
Now you're looking good man, let me tell you it wasn't you know
Why aren't you married Jake? What are you waiting for bro? What are you waiting for?
You're gonna sit in front of us forever. Just fucking you know acting get your as a girl
Get yourself some baby. I
Got baby kitty
Life is moving fast man. If we don't look up and you know look around us in a while. We're gonna miss it
Oh
And then even the cats that get off me dick like you need a girl not me, you know, you gotta hug a girl
Instead the cat is a substitute for a girl if you have a woman you can hug her and do that
And you play with a pussy and fuck her and have fun and choke up for you and you guys make a nice little life together
It's fun, man. Let me tell you it's good stuff
Until one day just comes crumbling down and kills
I'm kidding. I play
both roles like Eddie Murphy. He would play
Everybody and meet the clumps
Yeah
This is like her can leave me, you know, like you play all
Those are my favorite the actors that can do that like Martin Lawrence. Yo, yeah, I think it's like a drink
I think it's not even drinking shit
bottles empty
Nah, I don't tell me that
That's something
No, it's not no, it's not
It's almost
I'm taking his fucking hand of Georgie. There is water in there, bro. See you're a dick, Elias. Shut the fuck up. What a dick. There's water in there.
He's good, bro. He's not that good. Come on, Johnson, drinking an empty bottle.
Wow, you must have you shit you almost said I
Said I got it. I'll believe it honestly. What's the benefit to drink an empty bottle?
Choling us trolling and being funny. I'm a robot
Yo, you drunk
No, I drink water. I don't think he's drunk. I think he's just high on life. He's high on life Nick Johnson
Pissed off some right now
Johnson, how do you do it, bro? How do you do it? Like how do you have so much enthusiasm for life?
Like
What made you take this mother this motherfucker?
Dum-dums
You don't know what the fuck you guys are talking about at all.
Yeah
Yo, he robbed me tonight less
Literally robbed me tonight
I gave money and he didn't match it
That's
Your rich you don't care
I need to know our dollars
All right
You're 20 dumb frog
No, he said
Oh
What does that tell you I can fucking get you out of here
What does that tell you?
It tells me
This guy it's something
Give 40 bucks brother
He's choking on it's come you wake up choking on psyche's calm cool. Do you want to get do you want to be?
Can he do that always can you even do it do you want to see do you think
You guys want to see what kind of power up you what else kicked out?
Watch. Oh my god. Oh, you missed it. We are non-deal. We had non-deal at LDSs. Did you see non-deal?
No, I'm in my night, bro. Don't you
No, they kick the kid goes out
Yo, bro, I don't know what's crazy or non-deal or ghost
Non-deal, all right, that's a funny one. Oh ghost ghost is cheap ass
Motherfucker. Yeah, he's cheap as fuck and none of you has pink blacks. I mean, no
That's y'all he told me he told me yo kick this dude out and kick him out bro. I mean I didn't kick him out
Sorry, I like you you need to pay me to kick him out fuck that shit
Oh, it's gonna kick they kick Alex off
Yo psyche, I'm out of here, bro. So do that. Thank you for letting me up, bro. Have a good night
Nice to stop by on the cycle waking show
On the call of psyche show
you need to make some shirts and just say cult or psyche.
And then you can make ones that say like cult member
and then be like ones that say cult leader
and you can sell ones.
And so like you could be like, okay, a dad could buy one
that says cult leader and then he could have like five kids
and you go, oh shit, I'm gonna buy some of these
psych-awakening shirts.
You know what? Make them a
little coat and you can say, I
y'all my little coat, uh
followers or something.
He got five shirts for each
kid. 25 shirts. Boom. They
each need a shirt every day in
a week. You gotta go find the
Brady Bunch. Sell them shirts.
You did it
You left that you left that dildo plugged in that you got from Shaquille O'Neal
Shawn Puget
Yeah, right did you get my girl
Hey put the woman on the mic
Toby it kind of like right put the woman on
Ghost over
Why are you still here, dude? Why are you still here?
She said it's kind of late for you to be
Was that your mother sir
Three he's got funny too. Hey Nick Johnson lives alone. He doesn't have a mother does he?
I was why he's still here. I could kick you out. I'm a black man, I'm a white man.
Wait, son, did Nick Johnson, did we just hear a woman at Johnson's house?
I was his mother's.
That was his grandma. I think it was his grandma.
Mom, no, what mom would let him do when he's grown around the way he does.
Right, think about it. I'm not care about anything like my son can just do whatever
The Taj in New York like an asshole be on YouTube 24-7
No
Take them out for it. Just take them out of your retarded
Just be quiet just shut up brother just a little bit
What son of a beach
Let's say hi. Come on. Let's say hello ghost. Okay. Hello, sir. How are you? Thank you very much, sir
Let's have some manners, okay, we are not animals
Let's have some manners. Yeah, we're not we are animals, but let's have some manners. Okay
How you doing dumb dumb?
I'm doing good dum dum. How about you? Thank you sir pretty good pretty good
Now down fuck would you like to actually act I know what you're I know what you're doing for would you like to actually talk you want to run one
I don't know why he keeps mad at me up just to kick me every
Bye-bye Alex
Should we let Alex up here a more nose hockey the poor bummer fucking actually
You must feel like a football player, you get around in a
in a football match. Yeah, let me ask Apollo. Apollo, we
let him up here, like he's a firm on this and he's a
doctor. Should we let him wait a minute? Hold on. So,
Ghost, that's when Joe. Can't get him again. Can't get him
again. Apollo, what do you think? I don't know.
I don't know, I was here a few hours ago and someone showed his dick or whatever.
That was Alex should we let him up here? If you show your dick, what's Alex ever? Here's bargaining against fucking sighting
What would we ever leave back up here? You showed your dick in your porn mom, but what would we ever wait?
All right, so mean the back again I dare you
But he showed his dick and his porn bomber and he's a doxxer
So therefore he showed his dick on a fight on this panel and he also got
Put him backstage again. Let's have a talk. Yeah, I know. What do you think about that of all?
Well, yeah, he should be like why would we ever let him back and it'd be retarded first let him back up here, right?
He's another type of New York idiot. That's all I can say the old dogs. They're all bark. They're all
bullshit
I don't know why I have to follow back
You're telling me that you know, it's bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye
Okay, and retard
If Alex if Alice if he will put in the bag chat right now, it's like he says I promise not to porn bomb and I promise
Okay, but not the Docs. Oh, we can let him back up if he probably he puts it in the back at me promises that shit
He never will see should run back up if he promises it
And we're gonna believe him
Yeah, I mean I believe shit people in the back then yeah
Take cash cash and
You know, if you get $50, we'll
be back up for like 30 seconds.
I mean, I think that's a good
I'm talking. I have to call
I think we'll even give you 60
seconds, sir. Okay.
Guess I think about what you shouldn't bring your money to your piece of shit in your poor environment
You're a fucking retard. You're a degenerate. You know what the fuck you talked about you're a piece of shit
Oh, and also you want to ask people
You didn't even match my 20
You didn't even match my
You asked me to give you more.
How much money did I get?
I gave him $6.
I gave him a lot more money than that.
It's like how much money am I maybe you're over the like like
It's like type it in the back check I actually want to know over four figures
Over four figures. Okay. So this four figures mean I might be retarded. Can you guys explain does that mean like four?
I might be retarded in the bedroom and oh he gave what was it 20 dollars 30 dollars
How much money you have by a game over four figures, but 30 dollars my bad. Yeah, I'm a fucking retard
Over four figures for like that's in the thousands for yes, sir
And so I don't care five figures to match my 20 like you said you were
I mean if you give 20 and I get thousands of dollars
Drop 20 I'll match it. Thank you gave him six dollars after that. Oh, you match my 20, bro
I'm gonna find your fat ass and fucking it's not gonna be pretty bro. You know, I couldn't measure 20
Hey, psych
Where's the hamburgler? You ever seen the hamburger? That's good
The hamburger you know exactly what I'm talking about
Match my 20 you give them over for
That's what my money does. That's what those thousands of dollars do. I fucking stuff in my fingers. No, it's not
fucking dumb fuck
I ain't never gonna match your fucking a piece of shit
And Nick Johnson is also a piece of shit
What about me
What about me he was to be American so bad
Don't not drop down the power
Vader
Stop fucking yelling dude, it's okay to talk stop yelling
Jesus Christ shit fucking retards, right?
Could do that to me. You better don't start with me. Alex. I'm okay. You know that now. Well, let me know I would love that but I
Would love that my opinion but good
Apollo imagine Apollo dropping a penny that's that's funny. That's just yeah
Where's the thing that's
Who's that the board can any money for 20 years here
Who's that? The brokler in Brooklyn? With the scooter?
Money, would you like to join? Sir, you can join right now.
Yeah, come on, money, come on, Penel. Let's have a discussion.
I love talking with you.
You can join right now.
Different topics.
Wait a minute, Peter's live?
Yeah, we're just live right now, that's what I'm going to do, I'm going to go live, that's why, there's no way, bro, no one's watching, I don't believe it.
Why do you want him to go live on another person's live, dude?
No, bummer.
Ah, beat is going crazy, because like, he doesn't love her anymore.
Money's a pussy
Peter is in hell because psyche doesn't
I don't understand either man actually
But you say you sound like a mummy you sound like my 90-year-old grandma like
I
Actually Tony Bologna exactly my point
It doesn't give a psyche that beat that sucking our cock. Okay, cool. Why are you still here?
The question question, I think psyche might just be retarded what you're up here
The eaters live the dumb big nose Greek fucking two can't say that again
Why are you looking people here?
Look at those he gets so upset. Oh
You can't even match my 20 you fucking fat loser you love
You've been dropping hundreds every day and then when you actually make a contract with a man and say Alex
I'll match it. You do it. You didn't fulfill your contract, bro
Would you match my what at my donation, which was $20 you're supposed to match it with 20
And you even went as far as to say I'll even do 40 since your big bad ghost and you dropped six dollars
So I don't know what the oh my god
You know what I've only you did not match my donation and you're a liar in my book as of now
You know, I'm a winner. Well,
I literally made you get money
first.
How much money do you want to
compare? I just made you give
money. I win.
Oh, what's this crazy bitch
He rose weed in a prime day. Why are you still here?
It's actually a dose in case
It's so it's a walk
It's a dose that case
The most interesting man in the world
Don't say key my boy
By the way, my boy money for three is so fucking high
He missed places. Oh my boy. He's got two phones
Well, that's my boy. That's not your boy. First of all, he's a lover of second of all
You didn't match my 23rd of all why are you even talking bro?
I deserve to talk. I need to thank you a lot lying on his panel bro
The contract man you lied to me
You didn't match it boy. You didn't match anything
You paid sake you got played it's okay cuz when you die God's gonna you know take it out of your ass
Like remember that night you like to McQueen. I do. He's gonna take the pointy out of your ass
Don't worry about how much how much money did I get this time? How much money do you get?
You always get the asshole balanced that's why I like talking to you because it's easy when
You know, somewhere in the Amazon waiting for us, there's three out just for that to happen.
You know, somewhere there might be like a global ring, you know, factor in match to
20, so you're not a brand and a liar after tonight.
Cuz you're gonna be
About you, that's already clips and movies being made
But tonight you lied and you didn't give him nothing
Whatever you gave him in the past has nothing to do with tonight
Do you understand that?
We made a bet. You didn't keep your end of the promise.
Whatever you gave in the past means nothing.
Oh, nothing at all bro. We know is that you're a scumbag that didn't match my 20
So you match my 20 or shut the fuck up
Okay. I have a scary story. Okay. So, guys, I have a scary story goes. Listen, okay. Wait for a scary story. It's gonna be good.
Any marshmallows?
Yeah, it's gonna be really good. Okay. So, it's about what happened to McDonald's at a haunted McDonald's.
So, the story goes like this, one of the most famous urban legends originates from
Puerto Vaca, Mexico, where a haunted bench featuring a Ronald McDonald statue
is said to have caused a tragic incident.
According to the story, two young men were sitting on the bench
when one of them laid his head on Ronald's lap and heard it say,
I'm tired too.
The shocking event allegedly led to one man's death
from fright while the other fell into a coma.
The tale has, well, if one died from fright,
the other went to a coma.
How did they know the story?
But the tale has led to the removal of similar benches
from McDonald's locations across Mexico
due to the eerie rotation.
Well, just don't put your head in one's lap.
I mean, that's the first clue, okay?
So, well, well, well, well, well.
Yeah
Like taking some screws to his lap one night and just brought him home
Yeah, but you know it's too late now a ghostly woman in white has been said to be seen in the drive-thru in Sydney, Australia
And in Edoble, Oklahoma employees report mysterious voices
During the review the restaurant being built on an old cemetery
Oh, and also there's a little girl and that quiver can now about Mexico. I don't know if she's really did brought me down and saying, you know
I'm tired too or anything, but
So those are the stories. What do you think guys?
Think I could have brought it home
No problem. Can I ask a money for 20 a question? Yes
What up?
I'm money. What do you think about a lot of running like you see somebody crying in like a white dress in like the middle of nowhere
You know like run up to her
I'm probably gonna run away from it
I'm gonna go to happens
But what I'm not like that. Well, here's the difference between me and you I am gonna run a book
But guess what I got on my head. What if she offers you a blowjob money and she
I got
I'm legal to carry
I'm not leaving you man. I'm gonna catch some crazy
You talk about like all these scary movies and shit like I'm not gonna be there first of all
But if they jump out I'm a fucking putt three
About two in the heart
How scary does the ghost have to be to like not have sex with it?
But it said like be scared. I just want to know like the point
We're friends don't ask me during the ask questions like that. I told you that
Be respectful here
I know but I mean it's like woman give me a girl. I mean how and if you're a slide
How how many many you have to do to be gay? You see you ask them a little bit of a question stop doing that shit
Oh, I mean, I would I've had sex with like
I'm doing it dude. Be respectful. You're going down
It's goes to
Fuck out because you asked me weird ask questions stop doing that. I'm not saying you know that
That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it
So you got a love in a crash the fuck out in it
It's worth it
I'm gonna say it's worth it
She's stuck in my brain
Do I publish it to standard?
Shut up, Paul
You shut up fool
Shut the fuck up
Money
Money to keep
No I gotta tell you man
And somewhere goes about today
You should have money for 20 weeks in a month
Go down before you talk to me, mother, okay?
Cracking jokes, keeping us clean
The crowd starts howling
Bend your knee, bend your knee
We'll prove this in the crowd, son of a gun
Let's fucking go, and now we're flying
It's chaos with the halo, wild but true
Help me end this crap
Next time you are dressing with your highness, okay money
My name I am your highness
Dumb Dummy!
What's up, boss? I'm really proud of you.
Oh, I'm coming down. I'm up.
Do I permission to push out?
Ooh, ooh!
Let's go!
This is range IDK, what's that?
Beautiful
Beautiful song
Can we also see this Gretchen now?
Why are we missing the Gretchen now?
Turnin' pain into a doodle flame
May I have permission to crash out?
You already know
Ghost runs this town
Oh, I can see money for 20 dancing.
Move it, baby, move it.
Harry, hey, don't do that stuff.
I
Love that
What up faggots
You don't have fucking permission to do nothing asshole when I'm here
It's got even remember yet
Fagging out
that's a movie like
We got 20 people in here, dude. There's a big no way. No, I don't believe that
Everyone they've been boycotting psychoronies, right? It's been like
It's all because because Cody
Yeah, I heard nobody there's a room all there's a room on the streets
There's a room on the street
Wait, there's a room on the
It's not true
I didn't even understand what he said what you call him. He's a bitch
In the oh, okay. There's a rumor on the street. I got him from triple that's all
So you have to say
Triple that's all bro
You know, I like to take this time to tell God he's something. Yeah. Yeah, go ahead. Go ahead. Okay. I am Tony
Why no no shit. Oh, you are
I'm gonna send scrap metal to everybody. Hey, bro. We already know that goes to Ron. I
hope so. I love trying to let you like work yourself through it, you know, you want some
the drama, whatever you're having, you know, come for you pal. Send them in the world.
Your mom's fucking big labia. Yeah, my mom's big labia
That's enough for all of us
I fucking put my back and forth and fucking spicy my cheese
Can I call them that word yes, what's the F word?
Baggots oh that word has no meaning here
I came that there's not enough meaning. I owe my life. I called even my friends since I was 10 years old
Cool
I've been exciting
little fun thing let me take this time to apologize it's a fun thing I hope it's not you
let me take this time to apologize
Okay, so absolutely nobody is a fucking ghost is what the fuck we want some of the double chin. Yeah
Guys, okay, so I'm gonna do some horoscopes for the chat. Okay, so we're starting with Virgo. Who's a Virgo?
Make them real horoscopes make them horoscopes
Okay, so anyone a Virgo, okay, so what Virgo is called
Wait a minute before you start. I don't know what month is wits. What's month is me
Money for 20 this guy doesn't even know the months, bro
You might be a dumb dumb
I
Don't even know
I think we're over money
Give me one card
I want an animal card I will give you an animal card
I'll do it. I've been doing Virgo first. Okay. Okay. This is Virgo. You're gonna be
This Halloween you're gonna be going as the cursed librarian, so you're the rule of receipts my sorters and spreadsheets and the destroyer
Yeah
Paloalto is your Virgo you're glad to the party clutchy at Chris
A pure caffeine
Administrative assistant would doom the moment someone in miss close astrology your glasses flash
Goes I'm about to kick you out
Okay, hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Don't be rude.
Me. Where'd he go?
Oh wow, thing, thing that is amazin, Arrabidas, being amazin Arrabidas, the two little traitors.
Who cares, who cares?
No, I can't.
Wait till they come here in five minutes, okay?
Follow.
They won't be a lot here
Mason and think that is are both at beaters
It was beat it was beat up
some girl named
Be here in two minutes
Think that is all bold
Hero card, I love psyche though. He's my brother Apollo. You don't believe in tarot
Can you love your mother was not really what do you believe in?
Too much interpretation
You believe in Zeus
You don't believe in God, huh asshole. All right, you're gonna suffer
Maybe
Punish him
He's gonna get the cancer. Well, I can't help
Nick Johnson could give a fuck about any of us, right? What the hell is he doing?
He's watching the three
Fuck up, let me ask you a real-ass question is staying fucking shit over there join. He's watching prison movies
Is that Bruno? You're not even gonna answer me a fucking real question. That's the last thing that is. No, let's stay turn
That's the answer
God damn, can you not answer a fucking question?
That'd be a lot.
But hey, Alexander, I have to give you that. You played, we played with all these New York foods really good.
You played them all. This is chess, baby, not checkers.
Exactly checkmate upon you know he's the king in New York
Barking in each other for hours calling each other names. I will put you on the plate. What is that?
What was that
That's a joint what a surprise
The money for 20 you don't know what month month it is you understand
Money what day is it?
Today
Everything else out the window out the world is about to end and the money who cares I have a joint
Where's my weed a zombie outbreak anything you know people eating each other who cares I'm stoned
Well, I don't give a fuck I'm still your life
You're gonna blink and be 60 still in Brooklyn like wrong blood like
A fucking blink and I'm already almost 35
You gotta get busy living or get busy dying my man think of all the money they spent on this shit, too
Right, I spent it. Definitely. I spent over a million dollars on we since that's all
To your name and you suck the government's car for money. That's fucking crazy. That's good
I work that makes sense
ability
Fuck the governor. You live in a road filled apartment, but you spend a million dollars on weed. That's reparations
Like I have I don't have a pot to piss in my bridge is broken. There's roaches on my face
Like how does that so you gave up your life for weed basically is what you tell me that you said I pick weed over my life
Like I'm gonna be a bomb
Gloozer with no money and spend every millions millions of dollars. You just said a million dollars
marijuana
from books
Yeah, you gotta get food stamps to buy a fucking chopped cheese
No
No, so marijuana killed you drugs ruin your life, so it's true
ruin lives
Drugs ruin lives you should know yeah
Cocaine is a drug weed is a drug alcohol is a drug you spend all your money on
drugs at last he don't go around and have people
I'm talking about bums I'm talking about losers they can't afford it
I'm, you know, I can afford it, but I can walk around, I'm talking about bombs that spend millions and gave their life to the, to, to the drug, bro.
Yeah, look who is talking.
You don't think cigarettes are drugs? Every time you smoke that cigarette, you're a crackhead.
You think you're cool like we a little new poor pack the paper every time you take a cigarette out and spark a with the lighter
Your crack head. It's like smoking a crack pipe in my eyes
When I see people smoking a cigarette
Okay, are you doing?
Crack it you're doing cocaine right Alex I
Rather my cigarettes and weed then cracking coke
When you wrote so that means that means Apollo's a cigarette smoker Apollo you smoke cigarettes too. It's that way you can't breathe
Can't breathe cuz he smokes
You guys are all who whoever smokes cigarettes is the biggest loser on earth and the story and the story I don't know
Who you are what you think you are how much money you have or don't if you put a cigarette to your lips and light it up
Mother don't talk to me about cocaine crack or anything. That's $12 a pack. You're something
Cancer, it says when you bite cocaine, there's not a label on it like cocaine is gonna kill you
Label what is that? It's that's it on the box
Disco says cancer you're gonna die certain general you're gonna die
This is cancer and you just smoke it every day. I need another pack
New ports new ports, oh light it up you crickets that's a crackhead, bro
You're killing yourself
You're paying to kill yourself
A lot of money to buy a cake or steak to suck it all day
If you throw up all your money
You fucking crack it mother fuckers
Throw up all your money
That's the crack head
I don't smoke cigarettes
That's all
Right now on the plate
I don't smoke cigarettes
Do it
Yeah, but you do like two a day
I don't never smoke cigarettes in my life
You throw up everything you just ate on the plate
You guys are the crack heads
Do it do it
She's the guy who sniffing cocaine
Do it I don't smoke cigarettes bro in the Apollo if I watched him for cocaine
I would have to smoke cigarettes right because of you know, you need a cigarette up to a bump. I don't smoke cigarettes, bro
Cigarettes do not touch the body
You think I'm a moron?
I like fresh air, bro. My lungs doing that
You think I'm a fucking moron like you guys so get a cancer stick and paying for it. I do not
Apollo that's why you can't breathe there. So that's why you're a bum loser
Oh, how much the Germany of cigarettes course you probably suck on one every five seconds
You can't breathe bro, you can't even walk to the toilet without dying
I feel sorry for you people bro. What's wrong? I feel sorry
Nick go wash your fucking hands, dude
You don't give a fuck do you this guy don't care this this guy gave up
Okay, look how happy is he just gave up on life
Yeah, Nick. Oh, yeah, Nick is crazy
You don't go shit he goes a dumpster diver. He's a dumpster diving freak at night in the day. This is what he does
He's mentally ill, bro. He has mental problems. No one sees that
Well, that's a nice body his face is still ugly. He has a fucking giant nose. He's like his face is ugly
Nice body doesn't mean you're gonna get a girl, bro. Okay. You gotta have
If me and Nick were at a bar together, all the girls are flocking to me.
They're going to be like, who's this Pelican big nose dick?
This guy's a freak, bro. Oh, but I have abs. They don't give a fuck about abs, bro.
You can flip all the time if you want. As long as you have that face,
you know what you need to do is get a new face, bro. Not a new abs and chest.
You need a new face. And all the time flip is not going to get you a new face, Nick.
Yeah, you're still gonna be the same ugly little nerd
Look, how are you?
Honestly, what go look at them imagine like holding Nick Johnson by the cheese and kissing him like what?
No, no, no, they weren't hot Latinos like me man. Psych. Psych. He loves that. What are you talking about?
There's Louisa look at him. Just take another swig of the water
Jesus
But you know there is an ugly bitch out there for you Nick. I promise you there's definitely an ugly loser bitch like you
With the same kind of mentality like mental problems and you guys can work on the out together all crazy
Like it's me and Nick and they were both crazy and ugly
We have nice bodies, but we're all both ugly and you can have little ugly babies
Right, and then they can just put tires all day long together after they're both all ugly
You can have an ugly family of tire
What's the name Rachel Bartha? It's gonna be Gretchen or Bartha, bro Rachel
Rachel no no Gretchen Gretchen Gretchen something like that. Yeah, ugly. That'd be all these names a Gretchen
Nicking welcome to Nick and Gretchen's wedding
Shoot your shot to Nick come on up. Look at his dick
Going with the stupid props every day what he broke Jesus someone call the cops on this man
You know, I actually like when he masks up so I don't have to see his ugly face.
I like when he's like fucking out superman, no, the other day he was Iron Man.
I'm like, yeah, he's Iron Man.
Like I don't look, I don't have to see his ugly face when he's Iron Man.
But no tonight I do what there's another makeshift bond. We're gonna know sure Nick pizza box next to him
You can't make fun of
What girl will be next to this loser's girls just want to get fucked Nick
Imagine a girl next to you. She wouldn't want to be around that like the way
Like what the fuck well, he'll make a girl out of some hair he found somewhere
Stretching Gretchen, leave Gretchen alone.
Stretching Gretchen, there you go.
That's Nick Johnson's girl stretching Gretchen bro. Whoever halloween town is God bless you cuz you just made my whole week
Halloween town Halloween town just brought me out of a depression. I was gonna go to bed and cry for the next three days
But because of Halloween town
Stretching Gretchen comment
will make it at least till the next weekend so thank you Halloween tongue
stretching grass and then you go town Halloween town it's a lifesaver whoever
town is whoever Halloween town it's a lifesaver that shit will bring me out
of depression when I'm in traffic tomorrow you know just
contemplating death
Like should I just drive off this bridge right now and show a pencil in my eyeball?
I want to think of how we done
Hold on one second. I want to ask Apollo question. Apollo. Why do you come here?
Hmm
Reaction with idiots. Oh
So you'd like to you'd like to have an interaction with fools
Yep
Okay, that's all it's that's an honest answer
Hope go ahead Alex go back
All right, all right, so look how ugly Johnson is
Yeah, he is just sitting there a lot beef like Jesus
You know, that's it's a waste of a body because he has a hot body, but his face killed the whole thing like damn
That's what it's like
Is he jerking off a bond?
He found that in the trash
Of course, he found everything the fucking couch. He's sitting on you find the trash everything around him. Did you find the trash?
Hello
He's probably sitting in a dumpster right now. That's probably dumpster. He's wearing the hat everything
Oh, even the pictures. That's not his family those pictures. That's why he doesn't care about camming them up
He just saw those pictures in the trash and put them on the wall, bro
Nice how you got there, buddy, but what are you doing with the town supposed to
This is woman right there
Oh, that's Katie. No. Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's no. Oh, I haven't seen her in a while. Yeah, he eats her pussy sometimes
Why would you put it behind the couch?
Put her next to you. It's a date. Nick
Put her next to you bro, you just leave her back there like
So we go
He doesn't kick Nick I paid for dinner you leave me back in
KZ whoever KZ is is crazy
He's asking for a link
There you go get her swift
She can make it over the couch
He doesn't care. She could have been sort of bleeding. He doesn't give a fuck
What the fucking garbage stick just behind her. I mean come on. She's falling for him
Oh
Nicaronies bro, please
Do something
Damn it, but he's still cooking weed in his pot
You don't care about your girl dick behind you with drama to the back
Yes
He's just trading up from his hand
We need to what the wooden the wooden fucking the cardboard bitch the cardboard bitch that it just threw me on the couch. Yeah
That is a
Is he talking to himself?
He's talking to somebody. He's talking exactly. He is talking to somebody right?
He's crazy. I see his mouth moving. Oh, he's wearing a Michael Myers hat
I see who the hell is he talking to talking to her
Oh, okay
He's talking to her. Hello dick. I didn't catch on tonight. You're right. She's he got
That's why I'm coming here weird people. They make no sense
To her dick is but his hubby is his baby his it's how we love you
his
baby mama
Yeah, you can't find this kind of fucking content somewhere else only here. I don't think so. Yeah, I
agree no way
It's this guy, what's he watering bro, he's watering some things
He's building a bomb
He's water he just watered
He threw something out of stuck to her
He looks past bro. It's like toilet paper. He just watered
That's so far. How could you treat it that way Nick? That's fucking it. Come on Nick
It is at least after up dick. Can you stand there up? Nick Nick give her a kiss. Come on, man. Don't be like that
Give her a kiss Nick. Come on, man. Can you put it next to you on the couch dick give her a
Put it next to you hold it hold it like you love her. Yeah, put you there you go. There you go. There you go. Oh, Jesus
How she's fucking now she's looking over you
No, oh my god
What the fuck
This cat said I'm taking my socks off. This bitch is dead
Because her pussy pie smells like shit
It's a range did he cut it go. Yeah, he cut a hole right out of crotch you see the hole
There's a whole fucking cutout right at the end
There is
Wait, are you
Can you put a finger in the hole Nick Johnson just to confirm that's a hole
We need confirmation on the hole buddy. Is that a hole? Is that a shadow?
Well easy easy down fella down. Jesus. It's motherfuckers. Oh, we said was put it next to you. I'm fucking 69
You know what's funny the back of it looks like it's built right there's like old wood put together
Like did you build that Nick Johnson? I
Thought it was just some team who like cardboard things you know this guy built that thing
Yeah, put the molly socks back on pal your job is done. Oh poor fucking switch
What the fuck do you want coast where'd you come back up here if you're not gonna say shit fat boy ghost yeah
Fat boys not up here. He's fucking wasted
Oh, oh, he didn't match my 20 he's a pussy
the
Hakuna matata
There's a ruler back Nick Johnson is Jamie's Cowboys. I just got it. I just it just hit me
He's doing coke off her face
Oh
That I'm holding a bush for there is a whole there's a there's something he ripped the shit out of it. Yeah
This one's a ton on there put some cream in there
Some all over late
Maybe like a orange you like hollow out of orange
The finger in the hole with the finger in the hole
Tastes like cardboard
Eat that there you go, Nick. There you go. Eat that pussy
This is the best rebranding ever
We got 13
You can do bad in that we can do better than 13 people come on
Come on. Yeah, I got
One of your awesome stories
Yeah, when I was in World War II, there was this gay guy, you know, and the Germans didn't
like him.
The Germans didn't like him, and they wanted to put him in concentration camp, only because
he was gay.
What's your name?
Hans Rudolf.
Look at Nick, he took his hat off.
All right, hold on.
Look at Nick.
He escaped Argentina.
Look at Nick
Nazis the Nazis have them
Way to get all this hair
Exactly, bro. That's what I'm saying. Look at Nick. Have you ever seen Nick with Nick?
Okay, I'll accept that.
Can you shut up?
Let me finish.
You don't even remind me of our primer.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
You're done.
You might feel like the doors. Who's the guy from the doors? Jim. Matt. Jeff Morrison. Yeah, I love Jim Morrison. I
Would be him exactly like oh too bad you can't
I wanted you
He fucked his own mother
Just get through a day because I want to be like Chris Angel one day, and then it's like
Angel
Ghost left and discussed
Fucking it's ghost over man
We are you get the 20 from alexander make it 20 from alexander
Fucking coming around here throwing a brain or ghost place. You don't know the fucking place ghosts. We're gonna call ghost over
We don't need your money here right psyche you tell them psych. No, he needs it don't that's he'll get pissed
Don't say that. He'll be like yeah, dude. He doesn't money digs. Don't say that and let me go
You're on the panel
Okay
Yeah, well God doesn't the way to approach to
The situation I get where you're coming from, but I try to last night and you know, I think I actually got kicked cuz of it
Hey, Alexander
Was it you who bombed on the size was it you Alexander?
That was an accident
No, no, no, that wasn't me that wasn't me
Well, you okay because it was today. No that black heart that same black heart that was up. That wasn't me
Okay, no
It was my boo
No, I wouldn't use white talk honestly. I don't want to pull a black cop black. I was too scary like
19 inch white cock is enough. Oh, you don't need 20 inch black. That's you're gonna sleep for weeks. Oh
speaking on from experience
Look at God look at God look at psyche. He looks like he's looking at my dick right now
Look look how happy he is. He's here in spirit
Yo
God forbid something bad happens, so we're gonna keep the show going
For cycle rolling. Yeah, we'll get an AI version of it. Why do they hate psyches?
You know why they hate psyche because he's a happy guy. He's very happy. There you go
That's it. They're miserable. They the evil that just the evil. They can't see happiness. They can't see
Plus plus don't have boobs
They don't want people to succeed
The first record. That was my first record.
Jamie's Cowboys.
I love Jamie's Cowboys.
Never matter.
We don't have Katrina on the panel again. She's following me everywhere.
Oh, Katrina.
Seriously?
Can you get out of my ass, man?
I'm I'm gonna make a hot to say
Bro, I've seen her he panned up. She's actually like fat fat. How fat like oh shit really bad
Like what I'm talking like um like her arms look like like
You know when people are fat
Yeah
You know that's like real like like over over 200. Yes
Yeah, yeah summer picked her up one day because they were going to something and she was like
Oh, my best friend Katrina's coming and she picked up from the airport and they camped up and they drove in the car
Cammed up the whole time and I was like this is this
Like real fat. I'm not even like making fun of like, you know, like I call page fat like that's just me being funny
Like KZ stop bitching about the 20 bucks either pay to get the fuck out. All right. Don't be a fucking bum
Who where KZ complaining about 20 bucks?
What a pussy
Are you gonna put my house that's the team KG
But he's not $20, and he's dumb, you-you-you-you
It's $20, bro, what the fuck?
$20 fucking dollars
I wipe my ass with $20
You're not showing it off, like, kill yourself
I'm not joking, I used to wipe my ass with $20 bills
Just to prove a point
It's too late, bro.
Fuck, you're doing a bunch of white in my ass.
Is that me?
I was tonight
If you blame what you've been left with
You can't afford $20
He just said it
It's been a tough month
Unexpected expenses
I ain't taking that shit
That means you can't afford $20
What a loser
I'm claiming my divine right
Unholy I'm broken alive
In the light of the night
I'm claiming my divine right
Now, we don't have it all, you wear the false oracle, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked through you, I've looked
Can't see Santa for twenty dollars
Broke your ass, bitch
Broke mother fucker
Michael
Greg
I don't know what I'm talking about
You know what I mean?
Guys, I posted a link in the chat. Go show some support. It's my girl, you know.
Support your girl?
Yeah.
Why? How much is Chrissy?
No, it's Chrissy.
Oh, yeah, Chrissy.
Chrissy, who's Chrissy?
She's cute.
Go watch her. Go watch her.
Seriously.
She's cute. I'm not hitting anything. Any link you drop or I don't trust you. She's not cute.
Show me a picture of her. Show me a picture site. Okay, I'll get a picture.
Chrissy. She made a song, you know, about a good guy.
the
Here she comes
What the fuck
That's fucking you me that's you
That's Mr. Yumi, but there we go. That's my babe. She loves me
She made a whole song about me
Yes
God it's not a I I promise you
Apollo he has four eyebrows. She has four eyebrows. What's what's the meaning?
She has
And she has clean hair which is fake so I'm looking at a crown basically so what better than you with your body
of the
one of the
I know but it's but it's not I think the more general
It's commercial, you know, she's she's gonna make a lot of money with you, so
Seriously, she may she may she sings about me, you know
What do you mean about you a married German guy?
Yes
Oh, Harry, Harry the Greek God, that's a lovely guy.
Paz and France.
I'm not into Harry.
Harry, Harry the Greek.
Yeah, that is a good one.
J-Dodd, what are you doing up there?
Yo, what's up?
This is fucking bed time, dude.
J-Cat, you got me.
No, no, no, it's your bedtime, homeboy.
Oh my god, get ready for a...
Blackheart G is gonna come in, huh?
Yeah, come on, Blackheart G.
Get ready for Blackheart G, baby.
Is that the green one?
He has a different exiled one, call them.
his boyfriend exiled one call him and says oh he got timed out in the psyche's chat someone
gonna save me come save me so here come black rg we're back hello i'm warning you black rg will
be up here in two seconds guys yeah yeah let's see where that pussy black rg is ready for hell
And no hell, he just gets, he just gets, his dog just gets really great day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and day and night, and
Right as you ever heard him laugh with the black RG
The two little bitches in the chat the two little lesbians
So I can hear black RG don't laugh and next I won like a hillbilly freak
I'm making money and make it all the way.
Jdogg, Jdogg, he said one is gay.
Jdogg, do you call him gay dog?
No, he's not one of the gay.
He's not one of the gay.
A hundred percent.
No, hold on.
We got gay birth and gay dog.
He's a hundred percent gay.
You're adding to the gay list?
No, no, hold on.
I like the gay dog.
I'm sorry, gay dog, but you might as well
Who do we got?
It's black or G I'm putting my money with somebody else that was somebody else that was groovy Jimmy
No, that wasn't Jimmy
That was somebody else
So they're trying to pull on this freak. Yeah, that's what they're doing. They're coming up here trying to pour them on
Hard news the big shows eggs out one
Who knows that's that pig? Don't let me show that again. Is that Kate the turtle carry Kate and Barry the turtle?
Is that Kate?
Cuz I've heard she's that fat
That's Kate damn that sucked
So you ever that was a bit that fat
I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I didn't want to, I
Oh, actually the fat pig was horny as hell. Yeah. No, I left in the middle of it. Oh
She tossed you off cuz you gotta
Chop yourself in God because they'll tell you like a ride and what I had things to do
I left so in the middle of fucking the fat pig you like I'm out. Yeah. Yeah, she was too fat
I had to go you were like this bitch is too fat. I'm out of here. I gotta go
So halfway through you look at the watch and you're like
This pig she's nice. I was being nice. I'm wasting my time. That's my problem. I'm a nice guy
I got shit to do so but in the middle of it. I said, you know, I'm out of here. I got things to do Wow
By bitch. I never heard that before so her fatness Wow
Yeah, she's way too fat. We're out of there like this is too much fat for me plus the
The kind of how they didn't even get myself in this situation. I don't want to deal with this shit
I'm not even give actually get a fat bitch pregnant like that. That would do my god
Jesus, please don't ever say it again. Don't scare me like again. Oh
of that pig like that pregnant man
no psyche
I need to talk to you bear
I knew this little f**k was going on before
Zah, what happened now man, what's going on
do you approve of mods calling people
what's the beef
pet pedos in your chat
who did that, who said that sh**
that little homosexual J-Dog
he's gone now, we got rid of him, he's left
but someone change you, you are gay shit once
I'm gay. You've seen my chick dumbass
No, I don't I got a woman smash get your ass up if you got a problem
Smash isn't on you smash. No, it's smack somebody named smack. Oh smack smack
All right, I won't continue
not I was wondering if psyche approves of people calling someone a pedo in his
check right now nobody appears max come on come on up I think this has been an
issue for psyche in the past I'm just wondering does he like having those type
of issues he doesn't care
I think he'll suffer for the facts of people doing that shit then.
Oh, Smax is KZ trying to get up on the panel.
No, Smax is broken audit.
No, Smax is KZ.
You think so?
And Apollo, just in case you haven't seen her, that's my wife.
His wife is not a father.
I'm not like Jay Dogg. I don't go to gay bars for guys.
His wife is smoking.
How old is that picture though?
about four years
all right
not that old
I'll take your word for it that shouldn't gain like a hundred and fifty pounds or anything like that
it ain't been long since you've seen her on cam bro
she gave that much weight that quick boy
we're gonna have to get her on a weight loss program
you look damn good
I can't believe J-Dog ran off. He was talking all that smoke about get up here. I came up here J-Dog
Where you at?
He left J-Dog left. I know he's a fucking bitch. Is that him smacked his J-Dog?
No, I doubt it. Oh
Shit
That could be your wife
Don't let her eat too much man
Shit that woman does eat too much
That's
She's got nice feet
He wants to run it. That's close. Oh, it's look out cleaner feeder. Oh
My god better exactly
you can maybe in 30 what you call it you just call it a cut
a dirty feak on yeah
wow
her feel is kind of clean though
I don't see no dirt on this one
this one this one
that's ghost by the way that's ghost
stop doxing ghost bro
that's ghost
That's what we're gonna do the dude the chick the bitch the fat whale in the bed. That's cool
Come up or shut the fuck up Casey
Come on pay the $25 no one is that broke
All right, all right smash her pass Apollo smash her pass
My god, it's night. That's ghost again. Look it. We just smash it. We just smash it or would you pass it?
I want to smash
That's ghost bro, that's what he pays like he weighs, you know, they pay by the pound
It's like a sumo culture like tuna
You imagine having that bouncing on top. Yeah, holy fuck you did she break your hips. I
Don't know I date her if she pays what she weighs somebody's gonna fuck that right?
There's a man for every woman out there supposedly
Somebody's gonna stick their fish in that thing
She weighs I'm a millionaire straight away clumsy smash she pays actually weighs exactly
Whoa, they pay by the pound baby. That's a big I'm gonna have to throw that back. That's ghost
That's ghost
Ghost hold on
God you're gonna have to clip that okay. That's your next avatar
When goes no, no, no, no, it's too big
If you can't even put it you can even fit it in. Oh, here we go
Yeah
No, that's thank you with it's blonde wig. I'm gonna have to pass I want the fat chick
She's worth more money. You know, you know, she's white this woman. She's just really tan. That's tan mom
Shit yeah, look at those nips
Psychi I'm not gonna go at you for what J dog did but man you shouldn't be modern people putting fake jackets on people, bro
Who put what on who?
Jackets now
Dad, I'll call me a pedo Alex
What?
With no evidence with no evidence
Why there is no evidence?
JZ. I'm not good. I love you. No bueno
No, me gusta. He gets in his feelings too easily, bro
That's because that's uh, that's uh, you know, that's a jacket and a half to put a really easy
Yeah, J dogs not built for this shit
You saw his head though, you know, he can't blame the man. It's had his shape to hardly
It's a bump at the top of it like I've never seen a bald head with like a bump like it's
Not until we're not in that
That's cuz he was born out of an anus, bro. He's a asshole, baby
When he was coming out bro that head
Brings me bro. I haven't slept in a week
an asshole baby
Casey's a dick?
I like Casey, I didn't know he was a dick
Who's Casey? I don't even know who the fuck Casey is
Some freak, some free from hell
It's better off you don't know actually
Is he a junkie?
To be honest with you, I don't know who he is neither
but I know he don't like Jack Docky
Come on, you guys have been around
Is he a junkie? He's a junkie, right?
No, he's some dick that's on the panel
sucking his cock, I don't know what the fuck he is
Oh
KZ Herbie, what up kid?
Who the fuck is Irby for Tom? It's Irby
He see yeah, Irby is Irby Irby's to do
Who knows Jamie's car boys?
That's that girl a model girl. Yeah, she used to be a model. Yeah, like a Abercrombie and Fitch model. Oh, yeah
Burn baby burn who the hell is reality Nancy no one knows time
Anybody time time is cool people's times good. It's a girl or a guy. That's a woman. She's a real woman
He's all woman. Yeah with the dog avatar
100% woman a little pooch
She loves our puppy
She loves it's a she or a human human
You're awesome. She's a woman. That's a girl from where what state what that psycho bitch
She lives in Ohio, Ohio. I
Have a hater from Ohio
She hates you. Oh, well, she hates me some reason he man. He hates me, bro. I don't know why they did that bitch
That's crazy
how many form bombs did you get off this week Alex did you break a record
I did actually I broke my record
I did two at least how many did you get off Alex
a lot I heard about two of them
Oh, yes, and the money for 20
Yeah
Those were my only two actually so
These and I did cycle an accident site got it on the accident because I was trying to show pages 30 feet
And I press the wrong button and the cock pulled up
Yeah, that's one hell of a out
It is
You got a condo like he find me find me bro. He fired to pay for bombing him. He finds I would have find you too
That's not your girl, there's no way a hot girl like that would be weird don't matter slowly
Porkies
You wouldn't believe that
What the hell is this girl's name anyway for God?
He's a good painter this guy he ever sees paintings
No, I haven't yeah, what's his name Nick?
Johnson Nick is cool. Yeah, you're 24 yesterday. You said or the other day you were like leave Nick Johnson's leave
John Nick Johnson's alone something which
Live
Yo, it's dying you said it to say neither do I
He loves Nick Johnson Oh
The hell are we looking at was a promo ad I made
That's like he's asshole
Gay he's brainwashing us into gay land. He's trying
They just watch it's working with you Alex. It's kind of behind this ad here
Become gay are you gay yet Alex look at the screen
I don't care if you guys are gay as long as you're not a fag
Well, Jaydon's definitely a fag. So what do you mean?
Yeah, I'm mad about getting kicked out the gay club, bro. That's that's fag-like behavior
rainbow like
That's fag-like behavior
Fag-like behavior, I'm gonna have to steal that one. I think
I'm not trying to copy right now. You can have it. No, that's funny
Wait a minute. That's fact like behavior in my book. Let me check this. Yep
Statue 810.2 Oh fact like behavior. I like it
Psychies trying to turn us gay right now
He's been trying since we came here. Yeah, but where you been Alex
He's actually been quite successful with a few channel men
Huh?
Well, I don't want forget anything. What do you think's gonna happen first?
He's gonna turn you gay or that we're gonna destroy the channel first which one
Option two before option one. I think we're gonna turn
We're just gonna suck cock on the way down like
We're down to nine people now. Wow, this cult thing is working out great
the
None of your fat the ocean, please. We'll take the right limit off the panel. There won't be a weight limit come on up
All right
Wait a second wait nicks up to something hold on
Look, he's wiping his ass on the bed
Like the dog you don't see your dog like what is that?
Like his trance has worked
And he just drags his ass to and you're like what the fuck he doing
Oh Nick Johnson, oh
Shit Nick put that on put that mask on yeah, I was just gonna ask can you wear that?
Close your ears, we're gonna come become gay
Alex just put his headphones on full blast
Oh, no, not for the kids.
How creepy is that shit?
That's pretty creepy.
Can you imagine growing up watching that?
You know, they say the yellow one was a porn star. Tell the top East. That was my favorite. No
He's just fucked that la la. It was noo-noo-la la
Their names bro, tell the top use
They had a vacuum
Yeah, close your eyes and your ears you're gonna become gay if you don't blow you know
Even wake up with a dicking amount. You are now entering the world of gay
So now I figured it out. That's how J-Dog
Ended up that way
He pre-screened all these videos
Correct, you don't even know what's happening, bro. You just think whatever even nick left those two big one
It's just good programming one-on-one
if you if you play backwards you'll hear it it says like suck dick suck dick suck dick
second video cypher yeah if you really want a dick it's a message it's a message
that's why I pay so much for my weed it's counter reactive to that
Who was it up here that said they paid a million dollars for weed? That's crazy work. No, that was money
Damn money. That's a lot. I mean fucking dollars up in smoke
Gotty I'm gonna get out of here. I was just coming up here to fucking bash that gay boy J dog
he said
Come out the closet come out the closet 2025 J dawg give my best to your wife
Sure, dude
What does that mean you're the giant cock or like your best?
Hello, like you're gonna be specific
12 inch cock you're Johnson
This guy, you know, this guy should work for ice this Nick Johnson. Oh Johnson. Hell yeah
He could shoot him down all day. Exactly. Exactly. Definitely. It's his perfect job because he's a
party you just point them and tell them they run and
In between when they get when they get deported and all this shit gets thrown into the dumpster, you can go dumpster diamond
it's
it was easy again look at this he's got burritos up the ass this guy
Looks like a breakfast breeder from two days ago
He has a hoodie on he's got the hat on he looks again as a snowstorm. Oh, you put up his Mexican
Mexican flag is coming in. Yes. Here we go. Might as well. Cinco de Mayo. We go
It's it's October by the way, yeah, but for him it's fucking Cinco de Mayo
It's falling off. It just fell on him.
It just fell on him.
This way too, put him back up.
Before we start celebrating, okay?
He's making up with it now.
No, let him put it back up before he's celebrating.
He's springing the Mexican flag.
He's going to go to October.
That's such desecration. Stop stringing the flag, are you?
Yeah.
What is all that stuff behind behind them those that magazines like what is your stack of through like books books?
No, no, it's DVD looks like hoarding to me. Like that's a little like hoarding like right? Are you hoarding? Are you a hoarder?
I lost you in the hoarding
Must be feeding time oceans leaving
You know why I want to fuck spunky
Do you?
Yeah, I can arrange that for you. Can you yeah, I mean who are good friends
Are you?
Yeah, just don't mind
Yeah
He might watch a little bit, but he won't care yeah through the glass he can film
Bunkinator, he's so fun
Yeah, he's good people
He's not my type though
You got a pussy a pig and a hearty, right? That's my type
Well, you know what the lights are all you know, we won't see that which is yeah, but you can't give it a hepatitis
Oh god, so what she is that for Titus now?
Yeah, you're crazy spunky are you out there come in spunky now she's sleeping she's asleep I
Can't wait to talk to her
If you know what, guys, if you don't give up the tightest,
I'm sure you just, I'm sure you got it.
What a dick.
losing my fucking mind. I'm not gonna leave till I totally lose my fucking mind up here.
Who's ugly faces that on your picture? It looks like beat up, fat, and crazy.
Airplane mode I felt it in my skin
So I was sitting like designer gold
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing we've learned
Not to be solicial, but the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual, cause grief for me is silicone
I might have sent a picture from a mortal bed
Just to haunt you goddamn head
I knew you crave the chaos I fed, cause love like all they never did
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I want to crush you
I could never
It's fair, every wound you gave I wear
We take turns being the villains' muse
But damn it, I still wanna lose
Not to be celestial, but you made my claim perpetual
So I did something sexual, just to feel conceptual
I might've sent that photo from a stranger's lair
Not to be divine, but I love you
Even when I wanna push you
I could never
I was already broken
You can't forget
What was never spoken
Every scar
A holy mark
Every kiss
Another spark
Not to be divine
But I love you